Digital Marketing Executive



twinklec642@gmail.com



Bhagwati Garden Extn., Dwarka Mor



SUMMARY

A dedicated, strategic, and goal-oriented Digital Marketer with 1.8 years of expertise in Google Ads creating, implementing and optimizing campaigns. I am a fast learner, pro-active and adaptive to changes, a person who excels in creative, critical and copywriting skills. Seeking a position in a reputed firm to outshine in all that comes my way, considering all hurdles as challenges, improve my skill and work for the growth of the organisation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Media Buyer

Rein Digital PVT LTD | Sep 2022 - Present

- Plan, built, manage and execute Search Ads campaigns
- Managed Google Ads for 15 different clients at 6 figure monthly spend
- Have a bandwidth to manage around 45-50 campaigns altogether
- Led the development and execution of comprehensive digital marketing campaigns across Facebook Ads
- Identify trends with insights and optimize spend with performance based on the insights
- Focus on scaling and profitability for online sales & marketing
- Responsible for converting traffic on Google Ads platform, account planning & strategy
- Bid Management, Portfolio Optimization, Trend Prediction and Keyword Mining
- Account Optimizations- Budget, Bid, Account structure, Adcopies and more
- Responsible for handling B2C client marketing campaigns, from planning to optimization for DOTE. Co

Key Achievement- Improved profit margin and at the same time scaling the Google Ads account. Improved copywriting which lead to an increased CTR for clients. Increased the ROI as high as 10x along with the conversion and revenue by upto 5x.

Digital Marketing Intern

Online Strikers | June 2022 - Aug 2022

- Designed and executed social media strategy for LinkedIn, Facebook, Instagram and YouTube.
- Used Canva and Video Editing apps to create compelling visualizations that regularly had engagements.
- Developed and executed digital marketing techniques that greatly improved website ranking and drew in more potential customers.
- Manually audited client websites and launched promotional offers and events to attract new customers.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

- Proficiency in Google Ads
- Keyword Research
- Proficiency in Google Sheet Excel, Word & Power
- Creative Designing
- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- Experience in managing budgets and handling financial documents
- Identify Market Trend

EDUCATION

Deen Dayal Upadhyaya College, DU

Bachelor of Arts 2019- 2022

CERTIFICATIONS

Master in Digital Marketing (DIDM)

OPERATED TOOLS

- Google Keyword Planner
- · Google Trends
- Similar Web
- Canva Pro
- Poster My Wall
- Moz
- Copymatic AI Tools
- VEED.io
- Wordpress
- Google Analytics

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English

AWARDS

I was honored with an award of "The Best Team player" for an outstanding and best ever performance in the month of August- September 2023

HOBBIES

- Hand Ball & kabaddi
- Gym
- Dancing
- Reading Novels
- Cooking
- Curious to learn new things, experience new cultures, and meet new people
- Travelling
- Indian History
- Volunteerism
- Educating People about Fitness